tophits4u.com 2011-11-23

# TopHits4U

Information Collection and Use of Information 

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address). This information is used to contact the user about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others unless required by law - or in the case of members found to be actually or attempting to cheat or otherwise defraud tophits4u.com we may pass the members information on to other sites for the general protection of all. 

Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrators of this site can access personal information of the users. 

Correction/Updating Personal Information 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area. 

Right to Cancel 

Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this a link is provided at the end of system generated email messages from tophits4u.com, click the link and you will be taken to a web page where you may choose to be removed from the entire database. 

Site and Service Updates 

We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email. Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner 

**TopHits4U Member Advertisments:**

Feature Link: [**Finish FIRST with TJP !**](http://www.tophits4u.com/click.php?linkid=446)
